

NAMAN JAIN B.Tech. - CSE

Ph: +91-9414448642



2015

Email: 17ucs096@Inmiit.ac.in Jaipur, Rajasthan, India - 302031

BRIEF OVERVIEW / CAREER OBJECTIVE / SUMMARY

I'm a Pre-Final year student with the passion to develop Android Applications. I have worked on real-time projects. I love contributing to open source because it has taught so much to me. I also acquire keen knowledge of python and it's various libraries.

KEY EXPERTISE / SKILLS

Java Kotlin Python C Android Development Firebase MySQL Git Github Data Structures Algorithms

EDUCATION

 LNM Institute of Information Technology
 2017 - 2021

 B.Tech. - CSE | CGPA: 7.04 / 10.00
 CGPA: 7.04 / 10.00

 Samrat Public School, Ajmer

 12th | CBSE | Percentage: 83.20 / 100.00

10th | CISCE | Percentage: 89.30 / 100.00

AWARDS AND SCHOLARSHIPS

Emmanuel Mission School, Jalore

Merit Scholarship in 1st Year

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

LNM Institute of Information Technology

Teaching Assistant Computer Networks Lab

Fossasia, Kivy, Open Data Kit Jan. 1, 2019 - Present

Open Source Developer

Driliyo June 20, 2019 - Dec. 30, 2019

Lead Android Developer

Developed and managed the android platform for vehicle rental service from scratch to unite with nearby vendors. A platform featuring authentication, push notifications, refer and earn, live updates, location APIs and much more for both User and Vendor side.

INTERNSHIPS

Jan. 20, 2020 - Present

Jainam is a digital platform to connect all Jains across the whole world. I worked as a developer, tester and debugger. Solved many issues and worked on many features with peer mentors.

PROJECTS

Android App Development on Child Health

Jan. 1, 2020 - Dec. 1, 2020

Jan. 1, 2020 - Present

Mentor: Dr. Ashok Garai | Team Size: 2

Anti Ragging LNMIIT Oct. 20, 2019 - Nov. 20, 2020

Mentor: Shweta Bhandari | Team Size: 5

College-based android app to prevent ragging issues with features to communicate publicly and raise issues. Involves features like authentication, notifications, CRUD posts, SOS calling, location sharing, widgets, etc.

Religion Prediction of Country

Nov. 5, 2019 - Dec. 5, 2019

Mentor: Sakthi Balan | Team Size: 4

Religion detection of a country on the basis of various features like colors, figures, etc of a flag by using a flag dataset.

ACHIEVEMENTS

Runner up in Yellow Pages

ASSESSMENTS / CERTIFICATIONS

The Complete Python 3 Course: Beginner to Advanced

Android App Components - Intents, Activities, and Broadcast Receivers

Aggregate: 95.5 / 100.0

Android App Components - Services, Local IPC, and Content Providers

Aggregate: 100.0 / 100.0

Java for Android Aggregate: 100.0 / 100.0

SEMINARS / TRAININGS / WORKSHOPS

Artificial Intelligence Institute Name: TechieNest

PERSONAL INTERESTS / HOBBIES

- TV Series
- Gaming
- Travel

WEB LINKS

- Facebook https://facebook.com/naman653/
- Github https://github.com/naman653/
- LinkedIn https://www.linkedin.com/in/naman653/
- Codechef https://www.codechef.com/users/naman653/

PERSONAL DETAILS

Gender: Male

Marital Status: Unmarried

Current Address: LNMIIT, Hostel, Jaipur, Rajasthan, India - 302031

Date of Birth: Feb. 1, 2001 Known Languages: English, Hindi

Permanent Address: H No 4 Luniya Colony, Mitra Nagar, Vaishali Nagar Ajmer, State -Rajasthan, District -Ajmer, City -Ajmer, Pincode

-305004, Ajmer, Rajasthan, India - 305001

Phone Numbers: +91-9414448642, +91-8079005309

Emails: 17ucs096@Inmiit.ac.in, naman653@gmail.com